(
"ai_sub_version": "3.6.0",
"generated_at": "2026-10-05T00:27:36.567981",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"service_tier": null,
"service_tier_subtitles": null,
"service_tier_lyrics": null,
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
アソビ★まわり隊！ デビュー記念★歌枠リレー
[Asobi Mawari-tai! Debut Commemoration Singing Relay]
うち等！
We are...
アソビ！
Asobi...
まわり！
...Mawari...
隊！
...Tai!
のうちゃん！
No-chan!
お主ら、声聞こえてるかの？
Everyone, can you hear our voices?
どうかの？
How is it?
聞こえてますか？
Can you hear us?
どうかの？
How is it?
みんな！
Everyone!
大丈夫？今日子だけ声バカデカかった？
Is it okay? Was Kyoko's voice way too loud?
一応確認してから来てるんじゃが、どうかの？大丈夫かの？
We checked it beforehand, but how is it? Is it alright?
どうですか？
How is it?
うん、あ、みんな「たい！」って言ってくれてる！
Yeah, ah, everyone is saying "Tai!" in the chat!
ありがとう！「たい！」と一緒に。
Thank you! Along with "Tai!"
嬉しいね。
I'm so happy.
早速お主らがね、ちゃんとご挨拶をしてくれて嬉しいですね。ありがとう。
I'm glad you guys greeted us right away. Thank you.
さて、ということでですね、ここまで4人、わしたち4人が1人ずつ歌枠リレーやってまいりましたけれども、
Well, so, up until now, the four of us have done a singing relay one by one, but...
どうも！
Hello!
お主らいかがでしたか？
How did you guys like it?
どうだったかな？気になる。
How was it? I'm curious.
しかも、つづりと今日子はさ、歌枠初めてじゃん？
And besides, Tsuzuri and Kyoko, this was your first time doing a singing stream, right?
そう！そうなんです！
Yes! That's right!
初公開しちゃった。
We made our debut!
初公開よね。
Our first performance, right?
つづり、どうした？
Tsuzuri, how did it go?
つ、つづり上手かった？つづり...
W-Was Tsuzuri good? Tsuzuri...
いや、でも楽しかったです。
But it was really fun.
楽しかった？
Did you enjoy it?
え、なんかごめん、今日子、多分ね「下げすぎ」って言ってるんだけど、あのね、私が横向いちゃうと、マイクに声が乗らない仕様なのよ。
Oh, sorry, Kyoko... they're saying "it's too quiet" in chat, but you see, when I turn sideways, my voice doesn't get picked up by the mic.
で、私、みんなの目見て話したすぎて、横向いちゃうんだよね。
And since I want to look at everyone's eyes so much when talking, I keep turning sideways!
なるほど。
I see!
ごめんね。
Sorry about that!
そう、今日はこういうマイクだからね。
Yeah, we're using this kind of mic today.
そう、今日こういうマイク。これか、ちょっと今日子のマイクが低いかなって思うから、上げるの。
Yeah, this kind of mic. Ah, I thought Kyoko's mic was a bit too low, so I'll turn it up.
ありがとう、ありがとう。
Thank you, thank you.
これで届きやすくなったかの？
Is it easier to hear now?
ありがとう。
Thank you.
よしよしよし。
Alright, alright.
「つーちゃん上手だった」って言われてるよ。
They're saying "Tsu-chan was really good!"
みんな褒めてるよ、ほら。
Everyone is praising you, look!
えー、ありがとう！
Aw, thank you!
嬉しい、本当に。
I'm so happy, really.
ほら、「かっこよかった」って来てる！つづり「かっこよかった」って！
Look, someone said "you were so cool!" They said Tsuzuri was cool!
おお！
Oh!
え、かっこいい？
Eh, cool?
ほら、「つづり最高」って来てるよ！「つづり最高」って！
Look, they're saying "Tsuzuri is the best!"
え？楽しいな、歌枠。
Eh? Singing streams are so fun!
調子、調子乗り始めちゃう。
She's starting to get carried away!
と、いうことで、ちょっと今日の、お品書きを発表しちゃおうかなと思って。
And so, I thought I'd announce today's lineup!
おおー！
Ooh!
今日、あの、我々1人で歌ったんじゃが、今日はなんと、やっぱり
Today, we all sang solo, but today, as expected...
せっかく4人でこうやってね、揃ってるから、
Since the four of us are gathered together like this...
4人でコラボ歌枠もやっちゃったりしようかなって思ってるんじゃが、
I'm thinking we should also do a 4-person collab singing stream!
しかもしかも、今日はなんとグループ分け！グループ分けして、
And on top of that, we'll split into groups today!
2：2でコラボ歌枠みたいなのも見せようかなとか思ってるんじゃけど、どうかの？
We'll split into pairs and do a duo collab singing stream. How does that sound?
めっちゃいいじゃん！最高じゃん！
That's awesome! That's the best!
やっていきたいと思うんじゃが、
We'd love to do that...
えっ、まず、今日はちょっとお喋り、お喋りをして、
So first, we'll chat for a bit...
えっ、2人2人で歌って、
Then sing in pairs...
その後またお喋りして、
Then chat again...
4人で歌うって感じにしようって思ってるから、
And finally sing all four of us together.
お主ら最後まで、アソビまわりたい歌枠リレーをお見逃しなく！
So everyone, don't miss our Asobi Mawaritai Singing Relay until the very end!
泣く、泣く、泣く泣く！
I'm crying, I'm crying!
そしてそして、今見てくれてるお主ら、みんなのチャンネル登録は済んでおるかの？
And also, to all of you watching right now, have you already subscribed to everyone's channels?
メンバー全員の、ほかの新人のね。
To everyone's channels, including the other rookies!
高評価とチャンネル登録と、そして、ハッシュタグ「あそびまわりたい歌枠リレー」で...
Please like, subscribe, and use the hashtag #AsobimawaritaiUtawakuRelay...
ツイートいっぱいして欲しいのじゃ！
...to tweet lots and lots!
のじゃ、のじゃ、のじゃー！
Please do!
そうするとね、わしたち嬉しいからね。とっても嬉しい。あの、さっきもね、ほかのこの歌を聴きながら、めちゃ見てたからね。感想とかね。
That would make us so happy. So, so happy. Actually, we were looking at your comments just now while listening to the others sing.
めっちゃね、エゴサしてたよね。
We were totally egosearching.
ソフィアとわし2人でずっと見て...
Sophia and I were looking at them the whole time!
エゴサの鬼がいた。
そうそう、前半組がずっと見てた。
There was an egosearch demon.
Yeah, the first half group was watching the whole time.
ということで、今日そういえばさ、お主ら、秋葉原で昨日今日イベントあったの知ってる？
By the way, did you guys know that there was an event in Akihabara yesterday and today?
何があったよね、アキバに。
あそびまわりたいでさ、イベントあってさ。
Something was happening in Akihabara.
There was an "Asobimawaritai" event.
しかも今日さ、あの、ツズリとロピアが、なんかサプライズで...
And on top of that, today, Tsuzuri and Lopia did a surprise...
お！
ゲスト？何だっけあれ、ゲリラ出演？
Oh!
A guest appearance? What was it, a guerrilla appearance?
そう、ゲリラ出演、ゲリラ配信ね。
ゲリラ配信、そう現地の人とさ、こう意思疎通できるやつ、したって聞いたんじゃが。
Yeah, a guerrilla appearance, a guerrilla stream.
A guerrilla stream! I heard you did that thing where you can interact with the people on-site.
そうなんだよね。
That's right!
めっちゃ凄かったよね。
It was absolutely amazing!
本当にみんなの顔直接見れてね、わーって、本当にやり取りとかもさせていただいて...
We could see everyone's faces directly, and we got to interact with them...
凄く感動したなんか。本当にたくさんの方に応源いただいてるんだなってね。
...which was so moving. It made me realize how many people are actually supporting us.
そう、私、あ、本当にデビューしたんだなって改めて実感が湧いてて...
Yeah, it really hit me all over again that we've actually debuted...
めっちゃ楽しかったね。
It was so much fun!
ね、人間いたしの。
いっぱいいたよね。
Right, there were real humans there.
There were so many!
そう、あの、メラツとチョウコは、昨日にゲリラ出演してたんだよね。
そう、Day 1にね。
Right, Meratsu and Choko did their guerrilla appearance yesterday, right?
Yes, on Day 1!
どうだった？昨日は。
昨日は、あの、今日は割と匂わせしたじゃん、私とチョウコで。
How was it yesterday?
Well, Choko and I dropped quite a few hints today before doing it.
匂わせたけど、昨日全く匂わせなしのガチサプライズじゃったから、びっくりしたんじゃないのお主ら。
But yesterday was a complete surprise with zero hints, so you guys must have been shocked!
みんな早かったよ。始まった瞬間から、みんな、わーっと来てくれて。
本当に凄かったんだから。
Everyone was so fast! The moment we started, everyone came rushing over.
It was really incredible.
なんかあの、テープみたいのでさ、柵作られてるぐらい人集まってたよね。
そうそうそう。
There were so many people that they even had to set up barriers with tape.
Exactly.
確かに今日、そうだね。めっちゃいたよね、本当にそう思うと。
True, there were so many people today too, now that I think about it.
いいよね。しかもあの、何じゃっけ、あの、絶叫？絶叫じゃない。盛況？
That's great. And what was it again... "scream"? No, not screaming. Successful?
盛況すぎて、あのコインランドリーポーチさ、もう昼にはね...
It was so successful that the laundromat pouches, by noon, they were already...
そうそうそう、最初の方になくなっちゃったみたいな。
みんなやってくれてありがたいよね。噂を聞いてね。
Yeah, they sold out pretty early on.
It's so nice that everyone participated after hearing about it.
ソフィア、声ちっちゃい？ソフィア、上げれるかの？
どうやってあげるじゃん、こうか？
Sophia, is your voice a bit quiet? Can you turn Sophia up?
How do we do it, like this?
ソフィアのところを多分...よいしょ、よいしょ、よいしょ...
あ、ありがとう！ちょっと大きくなったかの？
Probably Sophia's volume slider... Here we go...
Ah, thank you! Did it get a bit louder?
あ、ありがとう！あ、聞こえる！
あ、よかった、聞こえる。ソフィアだ！ソフィアじゃ！
Ah, thank you! I can hear you!
Great, we can hear you. It's Sophia! Sophia's back!
ただいま、わーい！
I'm back, yay!
そう、それでさ、あの、スタンプさ、全部集めたけど、あの、交換できなかった人とかも、きっといると思うんじゃが。
Right, so about the stamps... I'm sure there were some people who collected them all but couldn't exchange them.
でもね、そんだけ大人気ってことは、きっとその頑張り、その大人気さ、あそびまわりたいの人気さをきっと、全世界が見ててくれてるってことじゃから。
But the fact that it was that popular means the world must be noticing how hard we worked and how popular Asobimawaritai is.
きっと次もね、次に繋がるはずじゃと思うのじゃ、わし。
繋がる、繋がる！
So I'm sure this will lead to the next big thing.
It definitely will!
だからさ、凄いのがさ、ポーチなくなったよってお知らせが出た後にも、まだ全然スタンプラリーやってくださる方がいっぱいいたの！
And what's amazing is that even after the announcement that the pouches were gone, so many people kept doing the stamp rally!
そうそうそう！
ね、嬉しい。ね、めちゃくちゃありがたいよね。
Exactly!
We're so happy. We're incredibly grateful!
しかも、楽しかったって！
そうそうそう、よかった。嬉しいの。
And they said they had fun!
Yes! I'm so glad. We're so happy.
本当にね、こういう声のおかげでね、また私たちの次なる企画がね、イベントだったりとか、そういうのが生まれるので。
Seriously, thanks to feedback like that, we can come up with our next projects or events.
本当にみんなから応援いただいて、ありがたかったね、今回は。
We really received so much support from everyone this time. Thank you so much.
ショッパーもいっぱい手に入れてくれてありがとうなのじゃ！
ありがとう！嬉しかったの。
Thank you so much for getting so many of our shopping bags, too!
Thank you! We're so happy.
あ、あとさあとさ、話変わっちゃうんだけど、今日の配信で私たち決めたいことあるんだよね。
ある、そう！
Oh, also, changing the subject, but there's something we need to decide on during today's stream.
There is, yes!
本当は前のコラボ配信で決めたかったんだけど...
楽しすぎてね！時間がね。
We actually wanted to decide on this during the last collab stream, but...
We had too much fun! We ran out of time.
そうそう、楽しすぎてね、本当にごめんなさい。
Yeah, we had way too much fun. I'm so sorry!
そう、何を決めたいかというと、結局「あそびまわりたい」の略称ってなんなんじゃ？
Right, so what we want to decide is... what on earth is the abbreviation for "Asobimawaritai"?
なんなんじゃ！なんなんじゃ結局。
なんか、色んなさ、候補があったじゃろ？
What is it?! What is it in the end?
There were various candidates, right?
なんじゃっけ、ツズリがわけわかんないこと言ってたやつあったよね。
あの恐ろしいやつね。怖かったよね。
What was it... there was that weird one that Tsuzuri suggested, right?
That terrifying one. It was scary.
え、違うよ！あれさ、チョウコがなんか「逆々」って言われてたからさ、私「あそびまわりたい」を逆に、なんか書いてディープしたらなんか、つーちゃんがおかしいみたいになっててびっくりしたんだけどあれ。
No, wait! Choko was talking about doing it "backwards", so I tried writing "Asobimawaritai" backwards and translating it deeply, and then it turned into some weird stuff about Tsu-chan. It shocked me!
解説聞いてもわかんないよ！
We still don't get it even after your explanation!
解説聞いてもわかんないのじゃ！
いきたびそう？ねえ、なんかさ、あれだったよね。
Even with the explanation, we have no idea!
Ikitabi-sou? Yeah, it was something like that, right?
気になった人はちょっとTwitterで私達のツイートを遡って頂いたら、つづりのやばいツイートが出てくると思う。
If you're curious, if you scroll back through our tweets on Twitter, I think you'll find Tuzuri's crazy tweets.
結構前だよね。デビュー前。そう、デビュー前。めっちゃ前。
It was quite a while ago, right? Before our debut. Yeah, before our debut. Way back.
で、この略称を配信の途中で決めようと思ってるから、お主ら考えておいて。
And, we're planning to decide on our abbreviation during the stream, so you guys think of some ideas.
いい略称考えておいて。
Think of a good abbreviation.
私達がね、歌ってる間に、お主ら達に考えておいて貰おうかなって。
While we are singing, we'd like you guys to think about it.
なんか候補出す？そしたら。確かに。何がいいかのう？
Should we suggest some candidates then? "True." "What would be good?"
うち等でさ、いいなって言ってたのは、あそびた。
One that we thought was good was "Asobita."
あ、そう、あそびた。あとはソフィアのひらめきで、あそびたいとか、あそまわとか。
Oh right, "Asobita." Also, based on Sophiya's inspiration, "Asobitai" or "Asomawa."
あそまわもいいね。つづり的には結構先輩も言ってくださってた、「あたい」って結構好きなんだけど。
"Asomawa" is good too. "As for Tuzuri, I quite like 'Atai' which our seniors also suggested."
あたい？あたい？あたい？うち等、なんかあたい！一人称混乱しちゃう。
Atai? Atai? Atai? For us, like, "Atai"! "We'll get confused about our pronouns!"
「あたい」ってなんか略し方、オタク略しみたいなのだじゃん。アニソンみたいな。
"Atai" sounds like an otaku-style abbreviation, doesn't it? Like an anime song, yeah.
確かに、確かに。
True, true.
みたいな候補かね。あとは、こより先輩が考えてくれた「あまたい」も素敵だよね。
Those are the candidates. Also, "Amatai" which Koyori-senpai thought up is wonderful too, right?
あまたい可愛い。あまたい可愛い、すごい可愛い。
"Amatai" is cute. "Amatai" is cute, super cute.
みたいな。他にもみんな思いついたら、ひらめいたら、ぜひぜひチャットしてもらえると嬉しいです。
Something like that. If everyone else thinks of something, has an inspiration, please feel free to chat about it.
教えて欲しいのじゃ。お願いします。
Please let us know. Please do.
さてさて、ここまでお喋りしてたけど、さっきまでも歌枠したし、そろそろ私達の歌、お主ら、聞きたいんじゃないの？
Well now, we've been chatting a bit up to here, but we were doing a singing stream earlier too, so shouldn't you guys be wanting to hear our song soon?
聞きたい！
We want to hear it!
お主が歌うんだよ！
You're the one singing!
私か？そうだよ、私達が歌うんだよ。そうか。
"Me?" "Yeah, we are the ones singing." "Oh, right."
聞きたいじゃろ？
You want to hear it, don't you?
あのね、チーム分けしてきたんだよね、今回。
You see, we've split into teams this time.
どうやってチーム分けしたか教えてあげる。考えてもらおうか、ちょっと。
I'll tell you how we split the teams. "Wait, let's have them think about it first."
あ、確かに確かに。合わせましょうっていうね。どういうチームでしょう？
Oh, indeed, indeed. Let's see if we match. "What kind of teams are we?"
4人でね、2-2で分かれたんじゃけど、誰と誰で分かれたと思う？
The four of us split 2-2, but who and who do you think split?
誰と誰だ？誰と誰だ？
Who and who? Who and who?
で、なんか、私達の中でチーム名みたいのも若干決まってる。呼び名がね。
And like, we also have kind of team names decided already. Nicknames.
呼び名があるんじゃけど、なんじゃと思う？
We have nicknames, but what do you think they are?
すっごい簡単な分け方をしたよね、うち等。なんじゃと思う？1日目、2日目だって。
We did a really simple way of splitting, didn't we? What do you think? Someone said 'Day 1 and Day 2'!
なるほどね。確かに、1日目さん、みたいなね。
I see. True, like 'the Day 1 group'.
なんかみんな、すごくさ、鋭くね？なかなか鋭いの。ひらめいてる。
Don't you think everyone is like, really sharp? "Quite sharp." "They're inspired."
ボケとツッコミとか書いてある。え、ボケとツッコミだったら何？どう分かれる？
Someone wrote 'Boke and Tsukkomi'. "Eh, if it's Boke and Tsukkomi, how would we split?"
つづりと、ボケで。つづりと、キョウコがツッコミでじゃないの？
"Tuzuri and... as Boke..." "Isn't it Tuzuri and Kyoko as Tsukkomi?"
真逆だろ！あ、今ツッコんじゃった、でも。
It's the exact opposite! "Ah, I just did a tsukkomi, though."
じゃあ、私ボケじゃん、その場合。何でや。
"Then I'm the boke in that case." "Why is that?"
ボケがつづり1人っていう可能性もあるな。
There's also a possibility that Tuzuri is the only boke.
いや、私も積極的にボケていくよ。
No, I'm going to actively make jokes too.
確かに、キョウコもボケてる、確かに。
True, Kyoko also acts as a boke, indeed.
じゃあ、ボケ組とツッコミ組かね。ボケ組？
Then, it's the Boke group and Tsukkomi group. Boke group?
そうだよ、つーちゃん、こっちおいで。やだー！
"That's right, Tsu-chan, come over here." "No way!"
人と人外だって、確かに。人間とそうじゃないものがいるの。
"Human and non-human, true." "We have humans and non-humans."
天然とヤバい方だって。え、それ？それ？天然とヤバい方、まあ両方つづりか。
"'Natural airhead' and 'dangerous one.' Eh, that? That? Natural airhead and the dangerous one... well, both are Tuzuri?"
え、何でよ？違うでしょ！1人しか該当してないじゃん、ワンマンチームだ。
"Eh, why? That's not it! Only one person fits that description, it's a one-man team."
え、1対3ってこと？1対3だったら、もう意味ないの。
"Eh, 1 vs 3? If it's 1 vs 3, it makes no sense."
そうそうそう、やっぱり2-2がいいよね。
Right, right, 2-2 is better after all.
で、つーちゃん、つーちゃん、今「お姉さん組」と「ポン組」って書いてあったけど、これどういう分け方かな？
And Tsu-chan, Tsu-chan, someone just wrote 'Older Sister Group' and 'Pon Group', but what kind of split would that be?
さすがにつづりがお姉さんで、意外とキョウコがポンなところがあるから、メラと私がお姉さんとか？
"As expected, Tuzuri is the older sister, and Kyoko surprisingly has clumsy parts, so Mela and I are the older sisters?"
どこがポンなのか言ってみろよ！
Tell me which part of me is clumsy!
ポンじゃない？どこがだよ！具体的に挙げてみろよ、じゃあ！
"Aren't you clumsy?" "Where! Name a specific example then!"
だって、この間の配信見てたら、結構ポンポン、これしてたよ。
But watching your stream the other day, you were doing clumsy things quite often.
何をしたんだよ！具体的に言ってよ、じゃあ！何も出ないじゃん、だって。
"What did I do! Tell me specifically then!" "See, you can't even name anything."
キョウコ可哀想じゃよ、つづりにそんなこと言われて。分かりきったことを聞くでない。
"Kyoko is pitiful, being told that by Tuzuri." "Don't ask things that are so obvious."
違う。でも結構ね、みんなキョウコ以外はちょっとポンなところがございますからね。
No. But actually, everyone besides Kyoko has some clumsy parts.
間違いない。1対3になっちゃうの。間違いない。
"No doubt." "So it becomes 1 vs 3." "No doubt."
じゃあ、そろそろ答え言っておくか。答えは、ええと。
Well then, shall we give the answer soon? The answer is, um...
キョウコとつづり。そして、メラとソフィア。で分かれてるんじゃが。
Kyoko and Tuzuri. And, Mela and Sophiya. That's how we're split, but...
暖色さん！はーい！
Warm colors! Present!
寒色さん！はーい！
Cool colors! Present!
色で分けておりますのじゃ。
We are split by colors!
私達、身長順とかさ、色分けとかさ、なんかめちゃ単純な多くない？
For us, height order, color splitting... aren't there too many super simple ones?
そうなんだよ。なんかさ、仲良し組で分けようとしても分けられないじゃん、正直。
Exactly. I mean, even if we tried to split by 'best friends', we honestly couldn't split, right?
そうかもそうかも。仲良しで2-2に分けられないから、うち等4人だからさ。必然的にそう言っちゃうよね。
"Maybe, maybe." "We can't split 2-2 by closeness because the four of us are so close." "So it naturally turns out that way."
確かに 確かに
Indeed, indeed.
うん うん
Yeah, yeah.
ということで 今日は暖色さんからお歌を歌ってもらおうかなって思うので
So, today, I think we'll have the Warm Colors Team sing for us,
一旦 歌うお部屋に移動しても良いかの？
so can we move over to the singing room?
お部屋！ 行くじゃん！
The room! Let's go!
ま、移動してマイクの本数が変わるだけなんですけど
Well, moving just changes the number of mics.
私たちが横にずれるから
Since we'll shift to the side...
よいしょ よいしょ
Up we go, up we go.
歌う二人が真ん中にいてもらいたくて マイクちょっと待ってね
We want the two singers in the middle. Hold on a bit with the mics.
うん
Okay.
これ つーちゃんこれさ あの 息合わせてさ
Tu-chan, for this, let's sync our breathing and...
どうもー！
Hello!
え、つづい、もう端っこから行かなきゃダメじゃん。はい、せーの、はい
Tsuzui, you have to enter from the very edge! Okay, ready, set, go!
どうもー！
Hello!
暖色さんチームです！
We are the Warm Colors Team!
何？漫才始まる？
What, is a comedy routine starting?
ちょっと待って！ツボらせないで！
Wait, don't make me laugh!
やばいやばい！
Oh my god, oh my god!
はー、落ち着いて。
Whew, calm down.
息が...
Out of breath...
いや、1回やってみたかったんだよね、これ。
I've always wanted to try doing that once.
確かに ちょっと憧れではあった
True, I did admire it a little.
でしょ？今日できたじゃん！やった！
Right? We got to do it today! Yay!
え、嬉しいなんか。
I'm kind of happy.
じゃあ、暖色さんチームにお歌を歌ってもらおうと思うので
Well then, since we're having the Warm Colors Team sing,
何て曲を歌うか教えてもらっても良いかの？
could you tell us what song you'll be singing?
発表しちゃう？ 行くよ？
Should we announce it? Ready?
せーの！ デパーチャー！
Ready, set, departure!
大地を踏みしめて
Taking a firm step on the earth,
君は目覚めていく
you are waking up.
天使の微笑みで
With an angel's smile,
連れ出して！
take me away!
孤独でも 一人じゃないさ
Even if you're lonely, you are not alone.
生まれてきたことに 必ず意味がある
There is surely a reason why you were born.
優しさに満ち溢れてる
Filled overflowing with kindness,
青い地球にありがとう
thank you to this blue planet.
You can smile again
太陽浴びて
bathed in the sun.
You can fly away
世界は君の 輝きを待ってる
the world is waiting for your shine.
大地を踏みしめて
Taking a firm step on the earth,
君は目覚めていく
you are waking up.
天使の微笑みで 連れ出して
With an angel's smile, take me away...
“始まり”はいつでも遅くないさ
It is never too late for a "beginning."
何度でも立ち上がれ！
Stand up again and again!
最後まで あきらめないさ
Don't give up until the very end.
やり続けることに 必ず意味がある
There is surely a reason to keep on trying.
You just try again
闇を抜けて
passing through the darkness.
You just go away
未来はいつも 僕たちを待ってる
the future is always waiting for us.
大空駆けぬけて
Soar through the vast sky,
海原越えて行け
and cross the wide open seas.
天使の投げキッス 捕まえて
Catch the angel's blown kiss.
まだ誰も見たことない世界へ
To a world that nobody has ever seen before,
飛び出そう 明日へ
let's fly out toward tomorrow!
大地を踏みしめて
Taking a firm step on the earth,
君は目覚めていく
you are waking up.
天使の微笑みで 連れ出して
With an angel's smile, take me away.
終わらない冒険に出掛けよう
Let's set out on an endless adventure,
いつまでも どこまでも
forever, wherever we may go!
流れ落ちる涙
The tears that overflow and fall,
勇気に変えていく
turn them into courage.
天使の羽広げ
Spread your angel wings,
舞い上がれ！
and soar high!
悲しみも痛みも 包み込んで
Embrace both the sadness and the pain,
強くなれ 明日
and become stronger tomorrow.
大地を踏みしめて
Step firmly upon the earth,
君は目覚めていく
And you will awaken.
天使の微笑みで
With an angel's smile,
連れ出して！
Take me away!
（you can smile!） 始まりはいつでも遅くないさ
(You can smile!) It's never too late to start.
（you can try!） 何度でも...
(You can try!) Again and again...
（you can try!） 何度でも立ち上がれ！
(You can try!) Rise up, time and time again!
イェーイ！
Yay!
拍手、拍手！
Applause, applause!
強化系、強化系...
Enhancer type, Enhancer type...
キョウコ星良メルエム言われてる
They say Kyoko and Seira are like Meruem.
星良はウボォーギンよ
Seira is Uvogin.
あ、確かに！ 強化系...
Ah, that's true! Enhancer type...
はっ！ってやつね
The one that goes, "Hah!"
めっちゃ強いやつ
The super strong one.
綴理、いるか？
Tsuzuri, are you there?
綴理はいます
Tsuzuri is here.
ここだけ決めらんと変な...
If we don't get this part right, it'll be weird...
はい、ハンターハンターのね、曲をね、大名曲
Yes, we sang that absolute masterpiece of a song from Hunter x Hunter.
歌いましたと
And that's that.
じゃ、そろそろ私達も歌っちゃおうかな！
Alright, should we sing soon too?
おー！ 楽しみだ
Oh! Looking forward to it.
にょき、にょき、にょき... マイク高いのじゃ
Pop, pop, pop... The mic is too high.
お、二人は「どうもー」って言わなくて大丈夫？
Oh, shouldn't you two say "Hello" first?
あ、確かに。やったほうがいいじゃん。やりたい？
Ah, true. We should do that. Do you want to?
やりたい！
I want to!
わかった、じゃあ...
Alright, then...
どうもー！
Hello!
寒色組でございます！
We are the Kanshoku-gumi!
おちゅめらなのじゃ
I'm Otsumera.
ソフィア・ヴァレンタインです！
And I'm Sophia Valentine!
どっちがボケ？
Who's the funny one?
え、それは... どっちだ？ ソフィア、ソフィアだぞ
Eh, well... which one is it? It's Sophia, Sophia!
いつも、いつもこの二人なんか争いあってるのじゃ
These two are always bickering over something.
メラちゃんとだったら、ソフィアがボケでいいかな
If it's with Mela-chan, Sophia can be the funny one.
え？ メラちゃんとだったら？ 誰とだったらダメなの？
Eh? If it's with Mela-chan? With whom would it not work?
え、それは綴理とならね、うちがツッコミやらな... ね、ね、ね
Well, if it's with Tsuzuri, I'd have to be the straight one...
噛んだ！噛んだ！みんな聞いた？噛んだぞ今！
She stuttered! Did everyone hear that? She stuttered just now!
ソフィア、そうなんでから...
Sophia is like that...
揚げ足取りがひどいのじゃ
You're so quick to point out mistakes.
もうええわ！ありがとうございましたー！
That's enough! Thank you very much!
終わっちゃったよ！まだこれからじゃ！
It's already over? We're just getting started!
歌って、歌って！
Sing, sing!
私達が歌う曲、せーので言う？
Shall we say the song we're singing on three?
せーの
One, two...
うまぴょい伝説！
Umapyoi Densetsu!
コールもね、二人にお願いするのじゃ
We'll ask you two to do the calls as well.
頑張る、負けない あれ？ 画面出ない
I'll do my best, won't lose! "Huh? The screen isn't showing."
出た！
It showed up!
位置について、よーい
On your marks, get set...
うーー（うまだっち！）
Ooh... (Umadacchi!)
うーー（うまぴょい！ うまぴょい！）
Ooh... (Umapyoi! Umapyoi!)
うーー（すきだっち！）
Ooh... (Sukidacchi!)
うーー（うまうまみゃーにゃ ３ ２ １ Fight!）
Ooh... (Uma-uma-mya-nya, 3, 2, 1, Fight!)
おひさまぱっぱか 快晴レース
The sun is shining bright for this clear-sky race!
ちょこちょこなにげに（So what? So what?）
Prancing along casually (So what? So what?)
第一第二第三表示に
On the first, second, and third displays...
だんだんだんだん出番が近づき
Step by step, our turn is getting closer!
めんたまギラギラ 出走です！
Eyes sparkling, it's time to race!
今日もめちゃめちゃはちゃめちゃだー！
Today is going to be incredibly chaotic!
がち追い込み（ごっつぁんです！）
A serious last-spurt drive (Thanks for the feast!)
コメくいてー（コメくいてー）でもやりたい！
I wanna eat rice! (I wanna eat rice!) But I want to do it anyway!
あのコは（ワッフォー）そのコは（どーよ）
That girl? (Waffle!) This girl? (What about her?)
どいつもこいつも あららんどー（りばんどー）
Every single one of them is in a muddle (Rebound!)
泣かないで（はいっ）くじけないで（はいっ）
Don't cry (Yes!) Don't lose heart (Yes!)
赤ちん塗っても（治らない！）
Even if you apply mercurochrome... (It won't heal!)
きょうの勝利の女神は
Today's goddess of victory...
あたしだけにチュッとする
...will blow a kiss just for me!
虹の彼方へゆこう
Let's head beyond the rainbow!
風を切って 大地けって きみのなかに 光ともす
Cutting through the wind, kicking off the earth, lighting up the hope inside of you.
（どきどきどきどきどきどきどきどき）
(Thump-thump-thump-thump-thump-thump!)
きみの愛馬が！
Your favorite horse...
ずきゅんどきゅん 走り出し（ふっふー）
...starts running with a bang! (Fuffuu!)
ばきゅんぶきゅん かけてゆーくーよー
Galloping away like a bullet!
こんなレースは はーじめて（３、２、１、Fight!）
I've never seen a race like this before! (3, 2, 1, Fight!)
ずきゅんどきゅん 胸が鳴り（ふっふー）
My heart beats with a bang! (Fuffuu!)
ばきゅんぶきゅん だいすきーだよー
I love you so, so much!
今日もかなでーるー
We're making sweet music today too,
はぴはぴだーりん（３、２、１、Go Fight!）
Our happy-happy darling! (3, 2, 1, Go Fight!)
うぴうぴはにー（３、２、１、）
Our upbeat honey! (3, 2, 1...)
うーー（Fight!）
Ooh... (Fight!)
うまだっち
Umadacchi!
うまぴょい うまぴょい
Umapyoi! Umapyoi!
うーー（オイっ）
Ooh... (Oi, oi!)
すったかたったったったったった（３、２、１、Fight!）
Galloping, galloping away! (3, 2, 1, Fight!)
あと５分（めざめのチュウ！）
Five more minutes! (A wake-up kiss!)
ねむーい（だるーい）
So sleepy... (So lazy...)
世紀の覚醒 二度寝三度寝
The awakening of the century! Second nap, third nap...
遅刻だ後追い！（馬場もぐんぐん！）
We're late! Chasing after them! (The track is getting better!)
すきすきすきすきすきすきしゅぎ
I love you, love you, love you, love you...
きみの愛馬が！ ずきんどきん 走り出し
Your beloved horse starts running, pit-a-pat!
ばきゅんぶきゅん かけてゆくよ
Galloping away, bang-bang!
こんなおもいはー はーじめて
It's my first time feeling this way...
3 2 1 Fight!
ずきんどきん 胸が鳴り
My heart is pounding,
ばきゅんぶきゅん だいすきーだよー
galloping, I love you so much!
今日もかなでる はぴはぴだーりん
Playing today as well, my happy, happy darling!
うぴうぴはにー 3 2 1 Fight!
Upi upi honey, 3, 2, 1, Fight!
さあ盛り上がってまいりました！まだまだまだまだ！
Alright, it's heating up! There's more to come!
はいはい いかす諸君 たいあんきちじつ
Yes yes, cool folks, on this very lucky day!
はいはい なりきりクイーン 黒板ひっかき
Yes yes, make-believe queen, scratching the blackboard!
ビート板 投げたら返ってきた 朝練中止で
Threw the kickboard and it came right back! Morning practice is canceled!
ジュビジュビファッ 走ったあとに ソーダ水（爆死）楽しかった
Shubi-dubi-fah! Drinking soda water after running (died of carbonation). That was fun!
そうだ、あとだしじゃんけんしよう
That's right, let's play rock-paper-scissors with a delay!
ださなきゃ負けよ じゃんけんしょい！
If you don't play, you lose! Jan-ken-shoy!
この気持ちー 届くならー 君のいろに 染まるよ
If these feelings reach you, I'll be dyed in your colors.
こんな あたしじゃ だーめだよね
A girl like me isn't good enough, is she?
うーーーー
Oooooh...
ずきんどきん 走り出し
Pit-a-pat, running out!
ばきゅんぶきゅん かけてゆくよ
Galloping away, bang-bang!
こんな レースは はーじめて
It's my first time in a race like this!
ずきんどきん 胸が鳴り
My heart is pounding!
ばきゅんぶきゅん だいすきーだよー
Galloping, I love you so much!
今日も かなでる
Playing today as well,
はぴはぴだーりん 3 2 1
my happy, happy darling! 3, 2, 1...
うぴうぴはにー 3 2 1 Fight!
Upi upi honey, 3, 2, 1, Fight!
ずきんどきん 走り出し
Pit-a-pat, running out!
ばきゅんぶきゅん かけてゆくよ
Galloping away, bang-bang!
こんな おもいは はーじめて
It's my first time feeling this way!
ずきんどきん 胸が鳴り
My heart is pounding!
ばきゅんぶきゅん だいすきーだよー
Galloping, I love you so much!
今日も かなでる
Playing today as well,
はぴはぴだーりん 3 2 1
my happy, happy darling! 3, 2, 1...
うぴうぴはにー 3 2 1 Fight!
Upi upi honey, 3, 2, 1, Fight!
よっしゃー！あはは
We did it! Ahahaha!
どうしたの？
What's wrong?
ううん、二人がめっちゃ可愛いと思って聴いてたのに
No, I was listening thinking you two were so cute,
ふとした時にコメント欄見たら
but when I casually glanced at the chat...
キョーコの合いの手で爆笑
I burst out laughing at Kyoko's call-and-response!
違う！だって二人が可愛いからさ、うおーってなっちゃうじゃん
No! It's because you two were so cute, I just couldn't help but go "Whoaa!"
わかるわかる、めっちゃ可愛かったの
I get it, I get it. You two were super cute!
すまんな、メラチとソフィアのオタクですまんな
Sorry, I can't help being a Melachi and Sophia otaku!
ありがとう
Thank you!
うまぴょい伝説を歌わせていただきました、のちょ
We just performed "Umapyoi Densetsu"!
じゃあ二人とも上に登ってこれるかの？にょきにょきと
Well then, can you two come up here? Grow up, grow up!
にょきにょき、あ、にょき！
Grow, grow! Ah, grow!
4人のとこ行く？
Shall we go to the four-person setup?
そうしよっか
Let's do that.
のいちゃー
Noicha~!
マイクの高さどうですか？みなさん。我々がもっと上がればいい？
How's the mic height, everyone? Do we need to raise ourselves?
ずいずいずいずいずい。これぐらい？いい感じだ？
Up, up, up, up... Around here? Is this good?
いい感じか？
Is it good?
よし！BGM、のいちゃ
Alright! BGM, Noicha!
お主らどうだった？
How did you guys like it?
コラボ歌聴くの初めてなんじゃない？
Isn't this the first time you've heard us sing a collab song?
ね、2-2初めてだよね
Yeah, it's the first time doing 2 and 2, right?
どうだった？
How was it?
どうだったかな？やばい、もう記憶が飛んでしまって...
How was it? Oh dear, my memory is already blanking out...
合いの手のせいで
All because of the call-and-response!
ごめんなさい、ツボっちゃった
I'm sorry, I couldn't stop laughing!
3 2 1 Fight!
しかもデカい！
And it was so loud!
色々貫通して脳内に直接来るもん、フィジカル的に
It bypassed everything and went straight into my brain, physically!
いやもう、ライブのつもりでやってるからさ
Well, I was doing it with a real live-concert mindset!
でもさ、よく二人噛まなかったね。あれつづり難すぎ
But really, it's amazing you two didn't stumble. The lyrics are way too fast.
難すぎ
So hard!
私だったら噛んでたかも
I definitely would've stumbled.
難しいよね。めっちゃ難しいよね
It is hard. Extremely hard, right?
しかも息もぴったりだったよ
And your breathing was perfectly in sync too!
息もすごかった。うれしい！
The breathing was amazing. I'm so happy!
え、ちょっと噛んじゃったけどバレてなかった？
Wait, I stumbled a tiny bit, but did nobody notice?
あ、大丈夫。気づいてない
Ah, you're fine. Nobody noticed.
合いの手に本気すぎてね、確かに
We were focusing too much on the shouting, honestly.
ダメだ、思い出したらツボっちゃう
Oh no, just thinking about it makes me laugh again.
全力コールだったからさ
Because it was a full-power chant.
なんかさ、私たちは今さ、横に実際にいるんだよね、今
You know, we're actually right next to each other right now.
オフコラボってやつ？
An off-collab, right?
オフコラボなんだけどさ、あの...
We're doing an off-collab, but...
うるさいんだよね！
...she's so loud!
キョーコが？
Kyoko is?
もううるさくてうるさくて！
So, so loud!
声がデカくて！
Her voice is huge!
どのくらいデカいかっていうとさ、4人で喋ってるじゃん。
To give you an idea of how loud she is, we're all talking together here...
あの、生だと下げれないから
But you can't turn down the volume live!
ね、ダイレクトアタック...
Yeah, it's a direct attack...
あのさ、ライブに行くときに、海外とかだと、もっと日本より音が大きいのね、ライブ
You know, when going to concerts, overseas ones are much louder than in Japan.
だから、耳壊さないように、イヤホン入れていくの
So, to protect your ears, you put in earplugs.
耳栓みたいな？ / そうそうそうそう。今日子に会うときそれ必須かも！
Like earplugs? / Yes, exactly. You might need them when meeting Kyoko!
今日子、グッズで、グッズで耳栓出して！ / あ、出そう！
Kyoko, release earplugs as merch! / Oh, let's do it!
それめっちゃいいじゃん！ / 出そう！ / 私と会うとき用！
That's so good! / Let's release them! / For use when meeting me!
ありがとう！ / カバーさん、お願いします！
Thank you! / Cover-san, please make it happen!
のっしゃーん！
Nosshaan!
そして、あの、歌をね、聴いてもらったところで、おぬしら歌聴きながら、まぁ歌に夢中で忘れてるかもしれないんじゃが
And now that you've heard our song, you might have forgotten because you were so focused on the song...
あの、略称ね。アソビマリティの略称を考える話があったんじゃが、覚えとるかの？
We had a discussion about deciding on an abbreviation for "Asobimariti", do you remember?
考えた？ / え、どうやって決める？そもそも
Did you think of any? / How are we going to decide anyway?
アンケート？ / かな？ / アンケートで決める？ / じゃあアンケートにさ、なんか闇鍋みたいに、1個さ、変なの入れて
A poll? / I guess? / Deciding with a poll? / Then, let's put in one weird choice, like a mystery pot.
ちょっと、それつーちゃんのやつじゃん！ / え、なんでだよ！
Hey, that's what Tsu-chan did! / What, why?!
それに、みんなの悪ノリでそれになったらどうするんですか！ / 確かに！あり得るよ、それ！
What if everyone votes for it as a joke! / True! That could happen!
確かに、確かに。じゃあ、ちょっと、一旦アンケートを新しくするか
True, true. Let's make a new poll then.
いや、うちらアソビマリティだからさ、多分リスナーさんとかもそういう遊び心持ってるからさ、危ないよ、それは
Well, since we're Asobimariti, our listeners probably have that playful spirit, so it's risky.
あり得るよ、あり得るよ。全然あり得るよ。 / え、じゃあ、4択まで選べるっぽいから
It's possible, totally possible. / Oh, since we can have up to four options...
ちょっとこの4つに何入れるかをさ、うちらでさ、考えよう
Let's think about what four choices we should put in.
アソビ... / ちょっと、わし打ち込んでるからさ、おぬしら喋ってて
Asobi... / I'm typing them in, so you guys keep talking.
やっぱりアソビタ欲しいな。 / アソビタ欲しいね。
I definitely want "Asobita." / "Asobita" is good.
なんかね、ビタミンみたいな感じ。すごい好き。 / ひらがなで「あそびた」？ / アソビタ
It sounds like vitamin. I really like it. / "Asobita" in hiragana? / "Asobita."
「あそびた」めっちゃ好き。 / つーちゃんは？
I really like "Asobita." / What about Tsu-chan?
あ、やっぱ「あたいおし」かな？ / あたいね！ / うちら「あたい」だよ
Oh, maybe "Ataioshi"? / "Atai", right! / We are "Atai"!
あたいはカタカナの「ア」に「タイ」でいいの？ / うんうんうん / あたい
For "Atai," is it katakana "A" and "tai"? / Yes, yes. / Atai.
あたい！え、びっくりマーク残し？あたいびっくりマーク？ / だってさ、うちら、あ、そう、うちらうちら
Atai! Wait, do we keep the exclamation mark? "Atai!"? / Because we, oh, right, we...
今何を考えてたか分かんなくなっちゃった。あたいあたい
Now I forgot what I was thinking about. "Atai", "Atai"...
アソビタとあたい入れてるな。あと2個どうする？この貴重な2枠。
We have "Asobita" and "Atai". What about the other two precious slots?
なんか、1個ずつ挙げてくれたから、うちらも1個ずつ挙げていこう
Since you two gave one each, let's also give one each.
ソピアは？ / えっとね、アソマワかな？ / アソマワ！
Sopia, what about you? / Let's see, maybe "Asomawa"? / "Asomawa"!
アソマワいいね！ / アソマワ王道で可愛いよね。全部ひらがなでいい？
"Asomawa" is good! / "Asomawa" is classic and cute. All in hiragana?
いや、アソだけカタカナで、マワはひらがなとかどうだ？ / 分かってる！分かってるソピアやっぱり！
How about "Aso" in katakana and "mawa" in hiragana? / You get it! Sopia, you really get it!
マワがひらがな / めちゃくちゃいい！
With "mawa" in hiragana. / That's so good!
ファンに人からも聞きたいよね / ねー！ / でも結構みんな、あまたいをしてるね
We should also ask the fans too. / Yeah! / But actually, many people are suggesting "Amatai".
あまたい。アソマワ。あまたい。あまだい？なんか...
"Amatai." "Asomawa." "Amatai." "Amadai"? Wait, some...
あまだいがいる！漢字であまだいがいる。 / あまだいいるね。
"Amadai" is there! Someone wrote "Amadai" in kanji. / Yes, there is "Amadai".
アソマワは結構いそうだよ / ね、アソマワもいるね
"Asomawa" seems to be quite popular. / Yeah, "Asomawa" is there too.
アンケートに入ってないやつの中だと多分「あまたい」が多そうかなっていう
Out of those not in the poll, "Amatai" seems to be the most common.
あまたい入れる？アリエんタイって言われてる、アリエんタイ！ / どこから？どこから来た？
Should we put "Amatai"? Someone said "Arientai"! / From where? Where did that come from?
どこだ？どこですか？
Where? Where is it?
知らない遠くから来たのじゃな / どこですか？違います。アソビマリティです。アリエんタイじゃないです！
It must have come from some unknown faraway place. / Where is it? No, we are Asobimariti. Not Arientai!
あの、アリエんの1人だけだからね？ / え？
There's only one "Arien" person, you know? / Eh?
ソピアあれかも、声ちっちゃいのね。マイクもっとこれぐらい近づくんじゃよ / おす！おす！こんなんでどうでしょう？
Sopia, maybe your voice is a bit quiet. Bring the mic closer, about this much. / Osu! Osu! How about this?
食べる勢いだから。マイクって食べていいんじゃよ / 食べるんだよ。 / わかった。
Like you're about to eat it. You can eat the mic, you know. / You're supposed to eat it. / Got it.
あとは、なんか、星とびっくりだけ残してる人いる！ / え？変な人間！変な人間！
Also, someone just put a star and an exclamation mark! / Eh? What a weird person! Weird person!
それさ、タグとかもめっちゃ使いづらいよね / 使いづらい。エゴサ...ね、エゴサのしやすさって大事
That would make the tag super hard to use. / Hard to use. Search... yeah, ease of searching is important.
大事！めっちゃ大事！マジで大事！ / うんうん
Important! Super important! Seriously important! / Yeah, yeah.
エゴサのしやすさか... / 使いやすさとかね。普段から使いやすいやつにしたいよね
Ease of searching, huh... / And usability. We want something easy to use daily.
ちょっと1個さ、聞いていい？アソマワさ、カタカナで「アソ」で「マワ」と全部ひらがなと、どっちがいいかちょっとさ、今みんなのあれで聞いてみていい？
Can I ask one thing? For "Asomawa", between "Aso" in katakana and "mawa" in hiragana, or all hiragana, can we ask everyone which they prefer right now?
それもなんか結構分かれるなって今ちょっと見てて思ったから / 確かに。アソマワ、でもやっぱり、あの、いちいち変換しないのが楽なんじゃな
Because looking at the chat, I thought opinions might be quite split. / True. But for "Asomawa", not having to convert characters is easier.
そうなんだよね。 / ひらがなアソマワは楽なんじゃな / 確かに。 / ひらがなも可愛いよね
That's true. / All-hiragana "Asomawa" is easier. / True. / Hiragana is cute too.
あ、アソビタイもまだあるね / アソビタイあるね。 / アソビタイも入れとく？
Oh, "Asobitai" is also there. / "Asobitai" is there. / Should we include "Asobitai" too?
アソビタイは打ちやすいから結構ね / まぁ打ちやすい / 打ちやすいよね。
Since "Asobitai" is quite easy to type. / Yeah, it's easy. / It is easy to type.
うんうん。あとね、まだ1個残ってるんじゃよ。今アソビタとあたいとアソマワと、あと1個の枠が残ってるんじゃが
Yeah, yeah. And we still have one slot left. Right now we have "Asobita", "Atai", "Asomawa", and one slot left.
何がいいかの？
What would be good?
うーん...
Hmm...
ひらがなアソマワ可愛い。 / ひらがな多いから、候補ひらがなに変えようか
All-hiragana "Asomawa" is cute. / Since there are many "hiragana" votes, should we change the option to hiragana?
ひらがなアソマワにね。かなり多いね。 / アソマワは分かりやすいしね、略が
Change it to all-hiragana "Asomawa". There are quite a lot. / "Asomawa" is easy to understand as an abbreviation.
ねえ、なんか、どんどんさ、アリエんタイ増えてきたんだけど！ / しかもさ、たまになんかエリントンタイもいるんだけど！
Hey, "Arientai" is starting to increase more and more! / And sometimes there's even "Ellingtontai"!
どういうことですか？違いますよ。
What do you mean by that? That's not it.
え、ふざけてありえん体入れたら1位になっちゃうからな。
Wait, if I jokingly put "unbelievable style," it'll get first place.
なっちゃう、やばいやばい！だめだめだめ！
It will! That's bad, bad! No, no, no!
そっか、吸われるもんね、正しい票がね。
Right, because it'll suck away the legitimate votes.
吸われる、吸われる。ソフィアがリスナーさん...って言おうとしたら噛んじゃった。
They'll get sucked away, yeah. Sophia tried to say "listeners," but stumbled.
これ、ちょっともう今日歌枠で、もうね...ヘロヘロね。
I had a singing stream today, so I'm already... worn out, right?
完全に。
Completely.
ウマ娘がんばったもんね。そうだよ、がんばったもん、すごかったもん！
You worked hard on Uma Musume, after all. Yeah, she did! It was amazing!
そこで滑舌、すみません、使い...もう終わりました、すみません。
My articulation is completely spent now, sorry...
ソフィア相当滑舌のね、必要な曲をいっぱい歌ったもんね。
Sophia sang a lot of songs that require serious articulation, after all.
かっこいい曲ね。確かに。確かに。ありがとう、ごめんね。
Cool songs, yeah. True. True. Thank you, sorry.
うーん、うーん。
Yeah, yeah.
いいよ、ふにゃふにゃしてて。ふにゃふにゃ、ふにゃふにゃ。
It's fine, being all floppy. Floppy, floppy.
やっぱ「遊びたい」かな？
As expected, maybe "I want to play"?
うん、「遊びたい」っぽいね、最後のは。「遊びたい」。
Yeah, it looks like "I want to play" is the last one. "I want to play."
多いのは「遊びたい」だね。じゃあ、よいしょ。
The most common one is "I want to play." Okay, then... up we go.
アンケートするのじゃ！
Let's do the poll!
みんな、でももうさ、「コイル」っていうさ、ちょっと危なそうなワードが出てきたんだけど、コイルはちょっと...
Everyone, but wait, a slightly dangerous word like "Coil" came up, but Coil is a bit...
いやー、コイル1位にさせるやつだろ？
Oh dear. That's the meme to vote Coil to first place, right?
そうそうそうそうそう！よかった、変な、やばい選択肢入れなくてよかった。
Exactly, exactly, exactly! Thank goodness. I'm glad I didn't put in weird, dangerous options.
ちゃんとね、あの、どれが選ばれてもいい選択肢4択をご用意いたしました。
I've prepared four options where any of them being chosen is perfectly fine.
じゃあ、アンケートをちょっと今からやるから、時間区切ろうか？
Then, I'll start the poll now, so should we set a time limit?
うん。どうしよう？59分までとか、3分間とかでやるか？
Yeah. What should we do? Until 59 minutes, or maybe run it for 3 minutes?
3分で。3分にしよ。スタート！
Let's do 3 minutes. Make it 3 minutes. Start!
今からアンケート送信します！おー！
Sending the poll now! Oh!
これ、え、ちづりも入れられるやつですか？入れられないやつですか？
Is this something Chizuri can vote in too? Or can I not?
これはわしの画面じゃから、わししか入れられん。入れられないのかー。
This is my screen, so only I can put it in. Can't vote, huh...
じゃあ、ここは、やっぱり皆さんに委ねよう！
Then, as expected, let's leave it to everyone else!
そうだね。ね。
That's right. Yeah.
だってつーちゃんもうあたいに1票入れてるんだから。
Because Tsu-chan already cast a vote for "Atai" (me).
え、そうだよ。あたいだよ。
Eh, that's right. I voted for "Atai."
確かに、あたいだよ。でも、でも、個人的には「遊びたい」はやっぱり好きだな。
True, it's Atai. But, but personally, I really like "I want to play."
うーん、うーん。
Yeah, yeah.
え、でもなんかどれでもね、いい感じだから。え、でもこれで決まるって結構、わ、ドキドキする！
But all of them seem pretty good. Still, knowing this will decide it is pretty exciting!
ドキドキする！確かに！ドキドキする。
Heart-pounding! Indeed! It is exciting.
どれになるかなー？みんな、どれになるかな？
Which one will it be? Everyone, which one will win?
どれになるかな？どれもいいからなー。
Which one will it be? Since they're all good.
これどうやったらさ、更新できるの？今、わしたちの画面0票になってるけど...
How do we refresh this? Currently, our screen says 0 votes...
あ、上がっていくはずだよね？うん、上がっていくはず。あれ、投票できないって言ってる？
Oh, it should be going up, right? Yeah, it should. Wait, are they saying they can't vote?
どこでこう...大丈夫そう？でも入れた人もいるよ。
Where do we... is it okay? But some people have voted.
入れた人いる？入れた？入れた？入れた！
Some people have? Did they? Did they? They voted!
あ、入れてる人いるな。うん、ちょっとじゃあ、もう1回起動するのじゃ。
Ah, looks like some people are voting. Yeah, let me try restarting it then.
そう。でもなんかちょっとラグったりしちゃうらしいから、しょうがないのかも。あ、そういう感じか。
Yeah. But apparently there can be some lag, so it might be unavoidable. Ah, is that how it is?
じゃあちょっと、ちょっと待ってやるのじゃ。
Then let's wait a little bit.
うーん、3分間...待ってやる。
Hmm, 3 minutes... We'll wait.
アンケートバグ、アンケートバグってる？あ、バグってるんだ。じゃあもう1回出し直してみるか。
Is the poll bugged? Is the poll bugging out? Ah, it is bugged. Then should we try resending it?
じゃあアンケートもう1回いくじゃん。ごめんなのじゃー！入れてくれた人ごめんね。
Then let's do the poll one more time. Sorry about that! Sorry to those who voted.
のじゃ？
Noja?
もう1回入れてね。あれ？ちょっと待ってね。
Please vote again. Huh? Hold on a second.
あ、こっちがバグってるってこと？入れたのにみんなのが反映されてないっていう感じなんだ。
Ah, does that mean our end is bugged? Like, they voted but it's not reflecting for everyone.
なるほど、なるほど。そういう感じか。一旦、終了するのじゃ。うん。
I see, I see. Is that how it is? Let me end it once. Yeah.
待って。のじゃ、のじゃ、のじゃ！がんばれ。
Wait. Noja, noja, noja! Do your best.
あれ？だめそう？
Huh? Is it not working?
あ、でもなんか、1.8万票入ってるよ。え、入ってる？あ、よかったよかった！ありがとう、みんな！
Oh, wait, it says 18,000 votes are in. Eh, they're in? Ah, thank goodness! Thank you, everyone!
え、入ってるけど、これで...もう1回、もう1回やる？もう1回やろう。やっぱ59分までって言ってたし。
Wait, they're in, but... should we do it one more time? Let's do it one more time. After all, we said until 59 minutes.
そう、そうだよね。じゃあじゃあ、もう1回...
Yes, that's right. Then, then, one more time...
えっと、え、待って。何て入れたか忘れちゃった。あ、ここに、ここに載ってるよ。
Um, wait. I forgot what options I put in. Oh, they're listed right here.
あ、あ、遊びた...あ、俺、今...
Ah, play... Ah, I just...
流れた、流れた。うん、でも覚えてる。任せろ。
It scrolled away. Yeah, but I remember. Leave it to me.
ちょっと待ってね。今からがんばってタイピングする。お主らもちょっと待っててくれる？
Hold on a moment. I'm going to type hard now. Can you guys wait for a bit?
待っててね。はーい。
Wait for us. Okay.
もう1回同じアンケート取ります。はい。
We'll run the exact same poll again. Yes.
遊びた...えっと、遊びたい。あたい、あたい、あたい。
"Asobita"... I mean, "Asobitai" (I want to play). Atai, Atai, Atai.
あそまわ。あたい、あたい、あたい、あたい...
"Asomawa." Atai, Atai, Atai, Atai...
なんか、今、最後の投票前の悪あがきしてる人たちがいる。
Seems like some people are making a last-minute struggle before the vote.
え？あ、「あそびた」「あそびたい」「あたい」。
Eh? Oh, "Asobita," "Asobitai," "Atai."
なんじゃ、あたい。あそまわ。
What's next, Atai? "Asomawa."
あそまわ。平仮名ね。
"Asomawa." In hiragana, right?
よし、もう1回いくのじゃ！よいしょー！よいしょー！
Alright, let's go one more time! Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
これで、これでいけるかの？さすがにいけてほしいのじゃ。いけてくれ。
Will this, will this work? I really hope it does. Please work.
お、きたきたきたきた！あ、反応した！いける、いける！すごい！はや！
Oh, here it comes! Ah, it reacted! It's working! Amazing! So fast!
よし、じゃあ時間は22...どうしようか？22:20までにする？そうしよっか。うん。
Alright, then the time is 22... What should we do? Make it until 22:20? Let's do that. Yeah.
22:20になったら切ろうと思いますのじゃ。わしの手元の時計じゃからね。お主らの時計じゃないよ。
I'll end it when it hits 22:20. That's by my own clock, by the way. Not your clocks.
うん、うん。わしが判断するからね。メラち基準で。うん。
Yeah, yeah. Because I'm the one who decides. By Merachi's standard. Yeah.
どうしよう、わしの時計が5時間遅れてたら...いや、待てるよ全然、5時間。
What if my clock is five hours behind... No, we can totally wait five hours.
本当？お主ら5時間、わしたちと一緒にいてくれる？
Really? Would you guys stay with us for five hours?
いけるか。耐久配信じゃん、もう。やっちゃうか？
Can we do it? That's basically an endurance stream. Shall we?
全然、今やっと喉慣れてきたからいけるけど、5時間。
Totally, my throat has finally warmed up now, so I can go for five hours.
お！こっから？こっから歌っちゃうか？5時間。歌っちゃうか？ね、そう...ぶっ通しでいくか？
Oh! From here? Shall we sing from here? For five hours? Shall we sing? Yeah, let's... go non-stop?
そんな、わし冗談で言ったのに、なんかこの2人本当にしそうで怖いのじゃ！
Wait, I only said that as a joke, but these two look like they'd actually do it, which is scary!
だって、うちうち...あそびまわりたい！！！
I mean, we... WANT TO PLAY AROUND!!!
これね、「遊びまわりたい」ゲームね。うん、とりあえずなんじゃよ。
That's the "I want to play around" game. Yeah, for now, that's what it is.
そしてそしてそして
And then, and then, and then...
えっとね、まだね、我の時計ね、なってない、10時
Wait, my clock hasn't hit 10:00 yet.
もうちょっと、あとね、見てあげよう、どれくらいか
Just a little more. Let me check how much time is left.
駆け込みだよみんな、あとちょっとだよ
It's the final rush, everyone! Just a little longer!
本当、あともうちょっとだぞ
Really, just a little more!
あとね、3秒！
And also, 3 seconds left!
3、2、1、急いで急いで！
3, 2, 1, hurry, hurry!
よし、終了！
Alright, time's up!
終了！
Time's up!
はい、結果は？えー、あそびたい52%！
Okay, and the results are... Um, "Asobitai" 52%!
おおー！結構ダントツ！
Oh! It's quite a landslide!
ダントツだったね。すごい、あそびたいだ！
It was a total landslide. Amazing, it's Asobitai!
はい、ちょっと固定コメントにしておこう
Yes, let me pin this comment.
略称は、略称は、あそび...
The abbreviation is, the abbreviation is, Asobi...
あそびたい、あそびあそびたい...
"Asobitai", "Asobi-Asobitai"...
あそびたいに決まったのじゃ！
It's decided to be Asobitai!
ついに決まったね。ありがとうみんな決めてくれて
It's finally decided! Thank you everyone for deciding.
投票してくれてありがとうなのじゃ
Thank you so much for voting!
2万票くらい集まったもんね
About 20,000 votes were gathered, right?
2.1万票だって！
They said 21,000 votes!
えー！そんなにいっぱいさ、そんなにいっぱい集めたらさ...
Wow, that many! Since we gathered that many...
これ、かなりあれじゃない？統計的に正しい値なんじゃない？
...isn't this statistically a highly accurate value?
確かに！母集団的に確かにいける
Indeed! In terms of population size, it definitely works.
これは「民意」と言っても過言ではない
It's no exaggeration to call this the public will.
よっしゃー！
Yes!
科学等裏付けもあるのじゃ！
We even have scientific backing!
じゃあ、我々「あそびたい」と名乗っていくのじゃ
Then we shall call ourselves "Asobitai".
肩書き「あそびたい」ね
Under the title "Asobitai".
あそびたい！エゴサも「あそびたい」ですることにするのじゃ
Asobitai! We'll use "Asobitai" for ego-searching too.
みんなに知ってほしいね。ハッシュタグとかも「あそびたい」で呟いてもらってもいいかもね
I want everyone to know. Maybe they can tweet using the hashtag "Asobitai" too.
割れるかな？どうなるかな？
Will it split? How will it go?
まあでも、全部調べるから！我らはエゴサの鬼だからね
Well, but we'll check all of them! Because we are beasts at ego-searching!
お主らさ、お主らのフォロワーにも教えてあげてよ
You guys, let your followers know too.
ハッシュタグ「#あそびまわりたい歌枠リレー」でさ
Using the hashtag "#AsobiMawaritaiUtawakuRelay"...
「あそびまわりたいの略称があそびたいになったらしいよ」みたいなのを呟いてフォロワーに教えてあげよう
Tweet something like, "Apparently the abbreviation for Asobi Mawaritai became Asobitai"!
お願いします！
お願いしますのじゃ！
Please do!
よしよしよし。そして名前が決まったところで
Alright, alright. Now that the name is decided...
お？
Oh?
やっぱお主らさ、せっかく集まってるんじゃから
After all, since we're all gathered here...
4人全員の歌ってるとこ見たくない？
Don't you want to see all four of us singing?
見たい！お主らが歌ううんじゃいよ！
We do! You guys are going to sing!
私たちが歌うんじゃいよ！
We are going to sing!
みんなの見たいという思いを代弁させていただいた
I spoke on behalf of everyone's desire to watch.
見たいよね？
You want to see it, right?
やっぱさ、4人で歌うならさ、ぴったりの曲がある気がするんじゃが
If we're singing as four, I feel like there's a perfect song...
お、なんだなんだ？なんじゃと思う？
Oh, what is it? What do you think it is?
最高の曲があるよね。最高の曲があるのじゃ
There's a supreme song. Yes, there is a supreme song.
お主らもきっと知ってるんじゃないの？知っててほしいのじゃ
You guys must know it too, right? I hope you know it.
よし、じゃあ夜も遅くなってきたし、歌っちゃおうかな？
Alright, since it's getting late, shall we sing?
歌おう！
Let's sing!
お水とか平気？お主ら
Are you guys okay with water?
飲むか
Let's drink.
エコー？
Echo?
エコー！ごきげんよう
Echo! Good day to you.
よしよしよし、それではお主ら...
Alright, alright. Now then, everyone...
よしよしに反応した。よしよし担当がよしよしに反応した
She reacted to "yoshi yoshi". The "yoshi yoshi" person reacted to it!
お姉さんだったのじゃ。置いとくか、よし
I was an older sister. Let's leave it at that. Alright.
ということで、みんなでタイトルコールしちゃう？
And with that, shall we do the title call together?
しちゃう！聞いてください、せーの！
Let's do it! Please listen. Ready, go!
さわげ！ぐるぐるタイム
Clamor! Round and Round Time
騒げる時間
Time to make a scene!
ドラムのロールが鳴った
The drum roll sounded!
遊びのフェスティバル始まっちゃう瞬間
The moment the play festival begins!
ゲームにおしゃべりカラオケ
Games, chatting, karaoke
それとも即興ライブ
Or an improvisational live performance!
ラララランドリーの扉を開けろ
La-la-la, open the laundry door!
行くぞ、お前ら！
Let's go, you guys!
お待たせしました　メンタルむきむき正義マン
Sorry to keep you waiting, mentally buff justice man!
ヒーローポリスのあとりたい
Hero Police Atori's turn!
火の用心！　火の用心！
Watch out for fire! Watch out for fire!
気楽に投稿　火事のもと
Posting casually is the source of flame wars!
指差し呼称で　おつかれさまでした、めっ！
Point and call, "Thank you for your hard work, no-no!"
お腹が空いたら　夜食食べた、めっ！
If you're hungry and eat a late-night snack, no-no!
小さな一歩
A small step
未来きっと
The future surely
地球は青いおにしんげっぽー
The Earth is blue, Onishin Geppo!
Let's go!
手と手合わせて
Put hands together
心重ねた
Our hearts overlapped
最強の仲間たちがここに集ったのなら
If the strongest comrades gathered here
ぐるぐるタイム始めよう
Let's start the round and round time
ぐるぐるもっと暴れろ
Round and round, run even more wild!
遊びの渦
The whirlpool of play
のせて 世界を洗え
Put us on, wash the world.
今日もアジトで騒ごう
Let's make some noise in our hideout today too!
うち等遊び回りたい
We want to play all around!
イェーイ！
Yeah!
フーフー！
Woo-hoo!
同じアホなら遊ばにゃ
If we're both fools, let's play!
ソンソン！
Son, son!
わんこそばなら食べなきゃ
If it's Wanko Soba, we gotta eat it!
損損！
Son, son!
カラフルポップのシティマッチ
A colorful pop city match,
ミストミスで泡立つち
bubbling up with mistakes.
顧客は総立ち、パパラッチ
Customers standing, paparazzi,
まあいっか
oh well!
ぐるぐるぐるぐる 踊りましょう！
Round and round and round... Let's dance!
ハイ！
Hey!
最高の非日常を追い求め
Chasing after the ultimate extraordinary life...
最強の仲間たちがここに集ったのなら
if the strongest friends have gathered here...
回る回る世界はきっとうち等と共に
the spinning world will surely spin with us!
ぐるぐるタイム始めよう
Let's start the Guruguru Time!
ぐるぐる猛進 暴れろ
Charge forward round and round, let's go wild!
遊びの渦で
In the whirlpool of play,
世界を洗え
wash the world!
今日もアジトで騒ぐぞ！
Today too, let's make some noise in our hideout!
ぐるぐるタイム 奏でよう
Let's play the Guruguru Time!
ぐるぐる猛進 弾けろ
Charge forward round and round, let's burst!
めちゃめちゃ楽しい
It's super fun,
わちゃわちゃ嬉しい
so happy and chaotic!
今日もアジトで騒ごう
Let's make some noise in our hideout today too!
うち等遊び回りたい
We want to play all around!
いつまででも楽しみたい
We want to have fun forever!
君も遊び回りたい！
You want to play all around too!
イェーイ！
Yeah!
フーフー！
Woo-hoo!
イェーイ！
Yeah!
フーフー！
Woo-hoo!
イェーイ！
Yeah!
フーフー！
Woo-hoo!
イェーイ！
Yeah!
フーフー！
Woo-hoo!
イェーイ！
Yeah!
のじゃ！
Noja!
はい。騒げ！ぐるぐるタイムでした！
Yes! That was "Sawage! Guruguru Time!"
聴いてくれてありがとうなのじゃ！
Thank you for listening, noja!
おぬしらはこの曲、知ってた？
Did you guys know this song?
知ってた？
Did you know?
もちろん知ってくれてるよね？
Of course you knew it, right?
うん！
Yeah!
生で歌うの初めてじゃったな。
It was our first time singing it live.
そうだ、初めてだ。
That's right, the first time!
ねえ。緊張するね。
Yeah, it makes you nervous.
超楽しかったよね！
It was super fun, right?
ライブとかめっちゃ盛り上がりそう！
It feels like it would be so hype at a live concert!
うん。いつかライブで歌いたいの。
Yeah. I want to sing it at a live concert...
それでさ、ライブで歌った後さ、この初めてのみんなで歌ったこの歌枠のリレーを聴いて、「あ、こんな頃もあったな」ってなるんじゃよ。
And then, after singing it live, we can listen to this first singing relay where we all sang together and think, "Ah, we had times like that too."
激エモだ！
That's super emotional!
うん。もう泣けてきた。
Yeah, I'm already about to cry.
早い。涙をとっておくのじゃ、おぬし。
Too fast! Keep your tears for later.
はい。ぐるぐるタイム歌わせていただきましたけど、そろそろね、お開きの時間にしようと思うんじゃが。
So, we sang "Sawage! Guruguru Time!" but it's about time to wrap things up.
ええ〜
Ehhh~
お知らタイムしちゃおうかなって思うからさ、おぬしらももうちょっと付き合ってよ。
But I'd like to do some announcement time, so please stay with us a bit longer.
お知らせさせてほしいのじゃ。
Let us share some announcements, noja.
えっとね、あ、そう、早速ね、
So, first of all...
ちょっとどこに出すのがいいんじゃろうか。この辺に出す？
Where should I display it? Around here?
ちょっとツズリとわしは隠れるけどいい？
Tsuzuri and I will be hidden, is that okay?
いいよ、頑張って上向いておいて。
That's fine! Try to look up.
はい。えっと、オリジナル曲「騒げ！ぐるぐるタイム！」、アソビまわり隊公式チャンネルにて公開中です！
Yes! The original song "Sawage! Guruguru Time!" is now available on the Asobimawaritai official channel!
さっきの曲聴いて、あ、また聴きたいなって思ったら、ぜひ何度もMVと合わせて聴いてください！
If you heard the song just now and want to listen again, please check it out along with the MV!
お願いします！
Please!
次！スターティングボイスが私たちの発売中じゃ！
Next! Our Starting Voice packs are now on sale!
英語と日本語両方ともあるので、かなりグローバルなボイスになってるんじゃないかなと思います。いろんなバリエーションのボイスが楽しめますので、ぜひお手に取ってください！
It has both English and Japanese, so it's a pretty global voice pack. You can enjoy many other variations, so please grab yours!
お願いします！
Please!
そして、動く壁紙！
And, animated PC wallpapers!
動く壁紙、早速もう壁紙にしてくれてるよって人もいっぱいいると思うんじゃが、我々のLive2D PVのイラストが壁紙になりましたので、こちらもぜひ合わせてお手に取っていただけると嬉しいですのじゃ！
Some of you might have already set it as your wallpaper, but the illustrations from our Live2D PV are now wallpapers. We'd be happy if you check them out too, noja!
お願いします！
Please!
そして次、こちら！レギュラーアウトフィットグッズですのじゃ。缶バッジとアクリルスタンド。
And next, here! It's our regular outfit goods, noja. Can badges and acrylic stands.
私たちの初期衣装のね、一番スタンダードなお顔を描かれてる缶バッジとアクリルスタンドが発売中ですので、常設グッズっぽいですが、今のうちにね、早めに手に入れて...
Can badges and acrylic stands featuring our debut outfits in standard poses are on sale! They seem to be permanent goods, but please get yours early...
あの、あの、いろんなところに連れて行ってくれてもいいんじゃないかなと思います。
I think it'd be great if you could take us to all kinds of places.
のちゃん、よろしくお願いします。
No-chan, please look forward to it!
よろしくお願いします！
Please look forward to it!
そして、あそびまわりたいのデビュー記念グッズですのじゃー！
And here are the debut commemorative goods for Asobimawaritai!
えっとね、これなんじゃっけ？あ、パネル？パネル？
Let's see, what was this again? Ah, a panel? A panel?
あ、アクリルパネル。アクリルパネルとか色紙とか、Tシャツとか、とにかくいろいろありますので、
Ah, acrylic panel. Acrylic panels, art boards, T-shirts, and lots of other things!
こちらも、あの、あそびまわりたいのグッズのページ見てみてほしいですのじゃ！
So we'd love for you to check out the Asobimawaritai goods page!
おねがいします！
Please do!
そして、ホロカ！ホロカ！ホロカ！
And then, Holoka! Holoka! Holoka!
声でっか！声でっか！あの、もう予約販売がね、始まってるっぽくて、
So loud! Your voice is so loud! It seems pre-orders have already started...
早速予約したよって人も見ますのじゃ。ぜひぜひ、あの、手に入れてくれると嬉しいですのじゃ！
And we've seen people saying they already pre-ordered. We'd be really happy if you got yours too!
のじゃ！そして、ここからはちょっと口頭での告知になってしまうんじゃが、
Indeed! And from here, we have some announcements to make verbally...
誰からいく？
Who's going first?
じゃあ、時系列順にいくか。
Then, shall we go in chronological order?
時系列？
Chronological?
あれ？ってことは、
Wait, in that case...
あたい？あたいから？あたいらか。
Me? From me? Or us?
あたいらだね。
It's us.
結構な、結構な告知じゃよな、これも。
This is a pretty big announcement too, right?
えっと、あたいら暖色さんチーム。
Well, we are the Warm Colors Team.
なんと、10月の6日、火曜日
On Tuesday, October 6th...
アンド、7日？7日かな？
And the 7th? Probably the 7th?
水曜日にかけて、オーバーウォッチ
over Wednesday, we'll be doing an Overwatch...
50勝、う、いや、50勝。
50 wins, uh, no, 50 wins.
それ、50勝耐久配信を行います！
That's right, we'll be doing a 50-win endurance stream!
耐久だよ！
An endurance stream!
え、あのさ、私オーバーウォッチ知らないんだけど、50勝ってどれくらいかかるのじゃ？
Um, I don't know much about Overwatch, but how long does it take to get 50 wins?
えっとね、私はもう達成してるのね。やった時は、25時間くらいかかったかな。
Well, I've already achieved it before. When I did it, it took about 25 hours.
え、のじゃ？え、はい？え？
Wait, what? Seriously? What?
25時間かかっちゃった。
It took 25 hours.
え、不眠？
Wait, without sleeping?
えっとね、日に分けた。何日かに分けてやったんだけど、合計で25時間かかったかな。
Well, I split it up. I did it over a few days, but in total it took about 25 hours.
はい、なるほど。頑張るのじゃ、応援よろしくお願いします。
I see. We'll do our best, so please support us!
はい、ちめらとつづりが頑張ります！応援してください！
Yes, Mera and Tsutsuri will do our best! Please support us!
頑張ります！配信のじゃ！
We'll do our best on stream!
頑張ってね。
Do your best.
二人でやればもっと早いはず。
If the two of you do it together, it should be faster.
はい！うち差し入れとか持って行こうか。
Yeah! Should I bring some snacks or something?
え、じゃあお手紙いっぱい届けて。
Oh, then send me lots of letters!
私から揚げがいい。
I want fried chicken!
なかなかの、結構いかつい耐久をデビュー直後にするの。
Doing such a tough endurance stream right after our debut, huh?
ね、そうだよね。うちありえんからね。
Right? That's unbelievable for us.
ありえん、ありえん「あそびまわりたい」か。なるほどね。
Unbelievable, unbelievable "Asobimawaritai", I see.
うん、うん。
Yeah, yeah.
でもいっぱい頑張れってきてるよ。
But we're getting lots of supportive messages!
頑張るね。
We'll do our best.
50勝してやろう。するぞ！
Let's get those 50 wins. We will!
じゃあ、わしたちの寒色さんチームのコラボの発表もしちゃおうかな。
Then, should we announce our Cool Colors Team's collaboration too?
知りたい！じゃあ、わしから言うね。
I want to know! I'll say it then.
えっと、ちょっと暖色さんが結構あの、重めじゃから、わしたちにも期待されるとちょっとそこまではお返しできないんじゃが、
Well, since the Warm Colors Team's stream is quite heavy, we don't want you to expect too much from us as we might not be able to deliver to that extent...
あの、すっごい優しく軽めのコラボなんじゃが、
It's a very gentle and light collaboration,
えっと、10月の8日、8日の木曜日に、
on Thursday, October 8th,
何時じゃっけ？えっとね、20時かな？
at what time was it? Ah, 8:00 PM?
8日の20時から、えっと、おとざさのチャンネルで、ソピアと「世界のアソビ大全」で戦いますのじゃ！
From 8:00 PM on the 8th, on Otozasa's channel, I will play Clubhouse Games with Sopia!
アソビ大全！やっぱ「あそびまわりたい」って名乗ってる以上ね、アソビ大全を是非ともやっておきたいゲーム。
Clubhouse Games! Since we call ourselves "Asobimawaritai", Clubhouse Games is a game we absolutely must play.
是非とも戦いたい、あの、うん、音笹の、ちよと、そらしなそぴあということで、最終決戦ね。
We definitely want to play... Otozasa's Chiyo and Sorashina Sopia, so it's a final showdown.
そう、ホロカではね、ボロ負けしたんで、
Yeah, since I totally lost in Holoca...
今度こそはリベンジをね、勝ち取ります。
I'll definitely get my revenge this time!
はい、したいと思いますのじゃ！
Yes, I plan to do so!
そして、ソピアからも告知あるんだよね。
And Sopia has an announcement too, right?
はい！ということで、その翌日、10月9日金曜日、空科ソピアのチャンネルで、
Yes! So, the next day, Friday, October 9th, on Sorashina Sopia's channel,
イグノーベル賞クイズ企画をやらせていただきます！ウィズあそびまわりたい！ということで、
we'll be doing an Ig Nobel Prize Quiz stream! With Asobimawaritai!
楽しみだ！次の4人コラボがそこかな。
Can't wait! That'll be our next four-person collaboration.
はい、夜21時から、10月9日夜21時から、イグノーベル賞って皆さん知ってるかな？
Yes, starting at 9:00 PM on October 9th. Do you all know about the Ig Nobel Prize?
そもそもノーベル賞っていうものがございまして、それは聞いたことある。
To begin with, there's the Nobel Prize, which I'm sure you've heard of.
なんかすごいね、色んな研究とか色んな形で人類に貢献した人に与えられるのがノーベル賞なんだけど、
It's a prize given to people who have contributed to humanity through various research or other ways,
その、パロディ賞っていうのがイグノーベル賞で、
and the parody of that is the Ig Nobel Prize.
パロディ。
A parody.
そうそう。なので、ノーベル賞とまた違って、人々を笑わせて、で、さらに考えさせるような、そんな研究とか取り組みに対して、
Right. So unlike the Nobel Prize, it's awarded for research or achievements that first make people laugh,
与えられる賞をイグノーベル賞って言って、
and then make them think.
結構ね、面白いなんか、ウォンバットは四角いうんちをするとかそういう、
There are really funny ones, like how wombats do square poops...
なにそれ！おもしろ！
What's that?! That's hilarious!
そうそう、そういうことを明らかにした人にイグノーベル賞が与えられたりとか、そういうね、ちょっとユニークな、
Yeah, the Ig Nobel Prize is awarded to people who discover things like that. So they are quite unique...
研究に関する賞に関する、
research-related awards...
ちょっとね、クイズをこの3人に出したいかなと思っているんで。
So I'd like to test these three with a quiz about it.
もう続き気になってるんだけど。
I'm already curious to hear more!
超おもしろいじゃん、イグノーベル賞。楽しみ、面白そう。ね。
The Ig Nobel Prize sounds super interesting! I'm looking forward to it, it seems fun. Right?
私がワクワクするクイズに答えるってこと？
Does that mean answering quizzes that get me excited?
超ワクワク！
Super exciting!
おー、そういうこと？
Oh, is that what it is?
クイズ番組なんかテレビみたいで憧れなのじゃ！
Doing a quiz show is like being on TV, I've always wanted to try it!
わかるわかる
I know, right?
超楽しみ！
I'm so excited!
楽しみなのじゃ！
I can't wait!
ということで、なんと次の4人コラボ
And so, our next collab with all four of us...
10月9日9時からそらしのソピアチャンネルでやりますので、ぜひぜひまた遊びに来てね！
...will be on October 9th at 9:00 PM on Sopia Sorashino's channel, so please come join us!
のじゃー！
Yay!
はーい、他にお知らせある人いる？大丈夫かな？
Alright, does anyone else have any announcements? Are we good?
大丈夫、うん、大丈夫
We're good, yep, we're good.
えっと、あそびまわり、えっと、デビューして...
Um, Asobimawari... we debuted...
1週間とちょっと？ちょっと！うん！
...about a week and a little more ago? Just a bit! Yeah!
これからわしたちのこと もっともっと応援よろしくお願いします
Please continue to support us more and more going forward!
あの、途中から歌枠リレー見たよって人は、もう一回最初から！
For those of you who tuned in halfway through the singing relay, watch it from the beginning!
最初から4人全員の歌枠アーカイブ聞いてくれると嬉しいですのじゃ！
We'd be happy if you listened to all four of our singing archives from the start!
みんな最高だったから本当に！
Everyone was seriously so amazing!
個性あったのー！ねー！うん！
Everyone was so unique! Right? Yeah!
うーん、みたいな感じで、今日はそろそろお開きに！
And with that, it's about time to wrap it up for today!
今来たばかり？寂しい？寂しいけど...
Did you just get here? Are you sad? It's sad, but...
アーカイブでさ、いつでも会えるからさ！確かに！
...you can always watch the archive to see us! True!
うん、きっと明日からのね、配信予定も
Yes, and our stream schedules starting tomorrow...
各々個人のTwitterとかで出ると思うから、お主らそちらもチェックしてみてほしいですのじゃ！
...will probably be posted on our individual Twitter accounts, so please check them out!
よろしくおねがいします！のじゃ！のじゃー！
Please check them out! Yay!
じゃあ最後は挨拶をね、えっと
Alright, let's do our final greeting... um...
次も、あそびまわり！って言ったら
...when I say, "Next time we'll also..."
みんなで、たーい！って言う挨拶をするよ！
...we'll all say "-tai!" for our greeting!
いいかの？準備いいかの？ばっちり！
Are you ready? Is everyone ready? Perfect!
よし、じゃあ最後の挨拶行きますのじゃ！次もみんなで、あそびまわり...
Alright, let's do our final greeting! Next time, all together, we'll...
たーい！
-tai!